[{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665471261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":449107,"timeElapsed":1480531},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665478441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7177,"timeElapsed":1487711},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665483180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4735,"timeElapsed":1492450},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665487785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4602,"timeElapsed":1497055},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665492573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4784,"timeElapsed":1501843},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665495852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3277,"timeElapsed":1505122},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665499279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3424,"timeElapsed":1508549},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665503830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4548,"timeElapsed":1513100},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665507715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3883,"timeElapsed":1516985},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665516526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5054,"timeElapsed":1525796},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665521022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4494,"timeElapsed":1530292},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665526128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5104,"timeElapsed":1535398},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665531026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4895,"timeElapsed":1540295},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665540296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9268,"timeElapsed":1549566},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665544006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":1553276},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665546822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2813,"timeElapsed":1556092},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665549524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":1558794},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665551959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2433,"timeElapsed":1561229},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665585929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":12212,"timeElapsed":1595199},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665588533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2602,"timeElapsed":1597803},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665593290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4754,"timeElapsed":1602559},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665596030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2738,"timeElapsed":1605300},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665598999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2966,"timeElapsed":1608268},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665601412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2410,"timeElapsed":1610682},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665603981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":1613250},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665607270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":1616540},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665609541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2268,"timeElapsed":1618811},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665683194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4660,"timeElapsed":1692464},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665685660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2464,"timeElapsed":1694930},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665687952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2290,"timeElapsed":1697222},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665690873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2918,"timeElapsed":1700143},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665693562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2686,"timeElapsed":1702831},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665696566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3002,"timeElapsed":1705836},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665700087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3519,"timeElapsed":1709357},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665702888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2800,"timeElapsed":1712158},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665705902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":1715172},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665709905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":1719174},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665712629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2722,"timeElapsed":1721899},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665715968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3336,"timeElapsed":1725238},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665722117,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6147,"timeElapsed":1731387},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665725802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":1735071},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665728301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2498,"timeElapsed":1737571},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665730491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":1739761},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665734982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4488,"timeElapsed":1744251},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665737390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2406,"timeElapsed":1746660},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665739915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2523,"timeElapsed":1749185},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665804031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11442,"timeElapsed":1813301},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665807974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3941,"timeElapsed":1817244},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665811362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3386,"timeElapsed":1820632},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665813727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2362,"timeElapsed":1822997},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665816479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2749,"timeElapsed":1825749},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665818223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1741,"timeElapsed":1827492},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665820805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2580,"timeElapsed":1830075},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665822936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":1832206},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665824828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1890,"timeElapsed":1834098},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665900394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":74504,"timeElapsed":1909664},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665903195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2798,"timeElapsed":1912465},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665906574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3377,"timeElapsed":1915844},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665909590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":1918860},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665912262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2669,"timeElapsed":1921532},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665914875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2610,"timeElapsed":1924145},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665917627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2749,"timeElapsed":1926896},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665919733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2104,"timeElapsed":1929003},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665922716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":1931986},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665930990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5971,"timeElapsed":1940260},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665934534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":1943804},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665937669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3132,"timeElapsed":1946939},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665940012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2340,"timeElapsed":1949282},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665942801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":1952071},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665945257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2454,"timeElapsed":1954527},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665947525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2266,"timeElapsed":1956795},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665951076,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3548,"timeElapsed":1960345},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665953401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2323,"timeElapsed":1962671},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665955658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":1964928},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666138898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":182249,"timeElapsed":2148167},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666141983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":2151253},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666146261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4276,"timeElapsed":2155531},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666148613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":2157883},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666157012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8396,"timeElapsed":2166282},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666159215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2200,"timeElapsed":2168485},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666185928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":26710,"timeElapsed":2195198},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666194141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8211,"timeElapsed":2203411},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666201455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7311,"timeElapsed":2210725},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666212377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10014,"timeElapsed":2221647},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666214964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":2224233},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666255612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":40646,"timeElapsed":2264882},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666260427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4813,"timeElapsed":2269696},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666271017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10589,"timeElapsed":2280287},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666273354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":2282624},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666277820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4464,"timeElapsed":2287090},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666282898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5075,"timeElapsed":2292168},{"subjectID":"x6xz3xs46v","prolificID":"667715b0cad8d06ec690ef00","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421519587592f258fbea6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666305896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":22996,"timeElapsed":2315166}]